Guide to the JDub Records Archive 2001-2011 MSS.330
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Commercial Media
  - Subseries A: Media
    - Ex-Centric Sound System - "West Nile Funk", Undated (Box 12)
    - Ex Lion Tamer - "Go Ghost", Undated (Box 12)
    - Eve's Women, 2002 (Box 12)
    - Family Junction - "Running Trains (we're huge in Japan), 2007 (Box 12)
    - Feinsmith Quartet - "Elohim", 2007 (Box 12)
    - Feldman, Lee - "I've Forgotten Everything", 2005 (Box 12)
    - Fogel, Shawn - "Millions of Miles Away", Undated (Box 12)
    - Fogel, Shawn - "One Day in the Desert", 2007 (Box 12)
    - Fools for April, 2006 (Box 12)
    - For a Change: Songs for Social Change, Undated (Box 12)
    - For Free Thinking People, vol. one, Undated (Box 12)
    - Fox-Rosen, Avi, Undated (Box 12)
    - Fox-Rosen, Avi - "Welcome to the Show", 2009 (Box 12)
    - Fox, Cantor Joel - "Oh Say Shalom", 1999 (Box 12)
    - Frolicking in the Garden of Paradox - an evening lecture with Rabbi Gershon Winkler, 2007 (Box 12)
    - Funk'n'Stein - The Band, 2005 (Box 12)
    - G., Eton - "South Side of the Synagogue", 2001 (Box 12)
    - Gabriel, Joshua - "21st Century Blues", 2005 (Box 12)
    - Garden State - "Shtetl Fabulous", 2005 (Box 12)
    - Gersh, Akiva - "The Only Truth I Know", 2004 (Box 12)
    - Gillis, Aram Rubenstein - "Side by Side", 2005 (Box 12)
    - Girls in Trouble - "Girls in Trouble", 2009 (Box 12)
    - Girls in Trouble - "Girls in Trouble" promo (2 copies), 2009 (Box 12)
    - Girls in Trouble - "Half You Half Me" (2 copies), 2011 (Box 12)
    - Girls in Trouble - "Half You Half Me" promo (2 copies), Undated (Box 12)
    - Girls Night On! - "Live at Makor", 2006 (Box 12)
    - The Glass Eye Trio - "Harajuku", 2006 (Box 12)
    - Glass, Seymour - "Note to Self", 2004 (Box 12)
    - Global Rhythm Collector's CD (featuring Matisyahu), 2005 (Box 12)
    - Gluckin, Tzvi - "Jewish Roots Music", 2006 (Box 12)
    - Gold, Ari - "Space Under Sun", 2004 (Box 12)
    - Golden Bloom - "March to the Drums", Undated (Box 12)
    - Golden Land - 2006 Sampler (Box 12)
    - Golem - "Citizen Boris" (2 copies), 2009 (Box 12)
    - Golem - "Citizen Boris" promo (2 copies), 2009 (Box 12)
    - Golem - "Fresh Off the Boat" (3 copies), 2006 (Box 12)
    - Golem - "Homesick Songs" (2 copies), 2004 (Box 12)
    - Golem - "Love Hurts", 2002 (Box 12)
    - Gostein, Abby - "Each Blessing", 2009 (Box 12)
    - Grey Egg - "Indoor Ski", 2007 (Box 12)
    - Habilium, 2003 (Box 12)
    - Hadash, Yom - "Take Me Back", 2006 (Box 12)
    - Handler, D.J. - "Y-Love, the Mixtape", Undated (Box 12)
    - Handler, D.J. - "Sephardic Music Festival Mixtape", Undated (Box 12)
    - Heffner, Daniel - "Heffrology", 2007 (Box 12)
    - Hello Tokyo - "Don't Cry in Public", 2006 (Box 12)
    - Hip Hop Hoodios - "Agua Pa' la Gente", 2005 (Box 12)
    - Hip Hop Shabbat, Undated (Box 12)
    - Human Haiku - "Every Good Boy", Undated (Box 12)
    - Hyim - "Let Out a Little Peace", 2003 (Box 12)
    - Ibn Gabirol - "Adumey Hasefatot", 2009 (Box 12)
    - Idan Raichel Project, The, 2006 (Box 12)
    - Idan Raichel Project - sampler, 2005 (Box 12)
    - Ikar - "When We Left for Our Journey...", 2007 (Box 12)
    - The Illtet, 2002 (Box 12)
    - Imo- "Happy Fatty", 2004 (Box 12)
    - Imo - "Moon Gazing", 1992 (Box 12)
    - Inner Light - "Spritual Electronic Music", Undated (Box 12)
    - Israel, Joseph - "Gone are the Days", 2005 (Box 12)
    - Israel Question, The - "Antithesis", 2003 (Box 12)
    - Israel Unlimited - "The Sound Exchange vol. 1", 2010 (Box 12)
    - Israel: A World of Music, 2003 (Box 12)
    - Israeli Ethnic Ensemble - "Erga", 2009 (Box 12)
    - Ivan Milev Band - "The Flight of the Krali Marco", 2005 (Box 12)
    - Izabo - "The Fun Makers", 2003 (Box 12)
    - J. Viewz - "The Besides EP", 2008 (Box 12)
    - J. Viewz - "Muse Breaks", 2007 (Box 12)
    - Jaffa Road - promotional CD (2 copies), 2007 (Box 12)
    - Jaffa Road - "Sun Place", 2009 (Box 12)
    - Jaro's Whisper, 2008 (Box 12)
    - Jew Da Maccabi - "Hello J Dub", Undated (Box 12)
    - Jew Tang Clan - "Stacks", Undated (Box 12)
      No Disk
    - Jody Grind, The - "Losing Time", 2004 (Box 12)
    - Jus-Goodie - "Freedom Song", 2004 (Box 12)
    - Kanter, Simcha - "Wellsprings", 2004 (Box 12)
    - Katamine - "Lag", 2005 (Box 12)
    - Katz, Yehuda - "Not Without You", Undated (Box 12)
    - Kirtan Rabbi - "Live", 2008 (Box 12)
    - Kirtan Rabbi - "One Thing I Seek", 2010 (Box 12)
    - Klez Dispensers - "New Jersey Freylekhs" (2 copies), 2003 (Box 12)
    - Klezfactor - "The Golem of Bathurst Manor" (2 copies), 2005 (Box 12)
    - Klezmatics - "Brother Moses Smote the Water", 2004 (Box 12)
    - Klezmatics - "Woody Guthrie's Happy Joyous Hanuka", Undated (Box 12)
    - Klezmer Juice - "ARC Music", 2005 (Box 12)
    - Klezmer Kidz - "Nashville Katzen", 2004 (Box 12)
    - Klezmer Revolution, 2008 (Box 12)
    - Kleztraphobix - "Another Bottle of Vodka", 2004 (Box 12)
    - Klez-X Remixed, 2006 (Box 12)
    - Kodesh, Aish - "Another Side of Jewish Music", Undated (Box 12)
    - Kohane of Newark - "New Midlife Crisis" (2 copies), 2008 (Box 12)
    - La Dolce Notte - Mixed by Hush Collective, 2009 (Box 12)
    - Laila, Chana - "Lion of Judah", 2009 (Box 12)
    - LaMoussia, Andra, 2005 (Box 12)
    - Lapidus, Benjamin - "Herencia Judia", 2007 (Box 12)
    - Laroz - "All Stars", 2003 (Box 12)
    - Lazer Lloyd and the Folk Spirit Blues - "Higher Ground", 2004 (Box 12)
    - Lazzar, David - "Shtark", 2004 (Box 13)
    - Ledgley, Yehuda - "The Quiz" (2 copies), 2005 (Box 13)
    - Leeds, Joanie - "City Kid!", 2008 (Box 13)
    - Leeds, Joanie - "Soul from My Footsteps", 2003 (Box 13)
    - LeeVees, The - "Hanukkah Rocks" (2 copies), 2005 (Box 13)
    - LeeVees, The - "Hanukkah Rocks" promo copy (3 copies), 2005 (Box 13)
    - L'Espeit du Klezmer - "Yankele", 2001 (Box 13)
    - Levy, Ross M. - "Where the Future Lies", 2005 (Box 13)
    - Lieberman, Steve (Gangsta Rabbi) - "Desert Fever Brigade", 2003 (Box 13)
    - Lieberman, Steve (Gangsta Rabbi) - "Diaspora", 2009 (Box 13)
    - Lieberman, Steve (Gangsta Rabbi) - "DiKtatoR 17" (2 copies), 2009 (Box 13)
    - Lieberman, Steve (Gangsta Rabbi) - "Jewish Engineer 18" (2 copies), 2010 (Box 13)
    - Lieberman, Steve (Gangsta Rabbi) - "Jewish Pirate", 2006 (Box 13)
    - Lieberman, Steve (Gangsta Rabbi) - "Melancholia Falling", 2006 (Box 13)
    - Lieberman, Steve (Gangsta Rabbi) - "Punkifier", 2005 (Box 13)
    - Lieberman, Steve (Gangsta Rabbi) - "Psych Ward", 2008 (Box 13)
    - Lieberman, Steve (Gangsta Rabbi) - "Shake the Missile Base", 2007 (Box 13)
    - Lieberman, Steve (Gangsta Rabbi) - "Viva the Gangsta Rabbi, Live" (2 copies), 2005 (Box 13)
    - Lockwood, Jeremiah - "American Primitive" (3 copies), 2005 (Box 13)
    - Lockwood, Jeremiah - "The Nigun Project", 2011 (Box 13)
    - London, Frank - "Divan Soundrack", Undated (Box 13)
    - Los Caparos - "Rasta Vasily", 2006 (Box 13)
    - Losben, Shwa - "Chop Chop", 2008 (Box 13)
    - Lost & Found - "Nexus", 2010 (Box 13)
    - Lubin, Noah - "Leaving Egypt", 2008 (Box 13)
    - Macaroons, The - "Let's Go Coconuts" (2 copies), 2009 (Box 13)
    - Machnai, Tami - "Levante", 2004 (Box 13)
    - Maimon and the Mongoose Band - "Third Ear" (2 copies), 2007 (Box 13)
    - Makkabees, The - "Vol. [alef]", Undated (Box 13)
    - Mama Doni - "Chanukah Fever" (2 copies), 2009 (Box 13)
    - Mama Doni - "I Love Herring", 2008 (Box 13)
    - Mama Doni - "I Love Purim", 2009 (Box 13)
    - Mames - "Babegenush", 2009 (Box 13)
    - Manach - "Twice the Light", Undated (Box 13)
    - Maple Street Project - "Chanukah on Maple Street", 2003 (Box 13)
    - Marie, Teena - "Congo Square", 2009 (Box 13)
    - Massias, Elie - "Brooklyn Days", Undated (Box 13)
    - Matisyahu - "Beastie Boy Remixes" (2 copies), Undated (Box 13)
    - Matisyahu - "King Without a Crown" (2 copies), 2005 (Box 13)
    - Matisyahu - "Night 1, Disc 1", Undated (Box 13)
    - Matisyahu - "Night 1, Disc 2", Undated (Box 13)
    - Matisyahu - "Night 2, Disc 1", Undated (Box 13)
    - Matisyahu - "Night 2, Disc 2", Undated (Box 13)
    - Matisyahu - "Shake off the Dust, Arise" (3 copies), 2004 (Box 13)
    - Matisyahu - "Shattered", 2008 (Box 13)
    - Matisyahu - "Youth" (2 copies), 2006 (Box 13)
    - Matisyahu - "Youth, Acapella", Undated (Box 13)
    - Matisyahu - "Youth Dub" (2 copies), 2006 (Box 13)
    - Matisyahu - "Youth" single edit (2 copies), 2006 (Box 13)
    - Mazal - "Axerico en Selanik", Undated (Box 13)
    - Medida - "Apple S Apple Z", Undated (Box 13)
    - Mellow Mool - "An Evening of...", 2007 (Box 13)
    - Mendi - "Dreamer" (2 CDs in case), Undated (Box 13)
    - Mendilow, Guy - "Live", 2005 (Box 13)
    - Mens Rea, Undated (Box 13)
    - Meshugga Beach Party, 2005 (Box 13)
    - Meyer, Yael - "Common Ground", 2004 (Box 13)
    - Miklatak - "Avadon Dub", Undated (Box 13)
    - Miriam - "Angel Song", 2005 (Box 13)
    - Miraim - "Call from the Narrows", 2007 (Box 13)
    - Miriam - "Light out of Darkness", 2003 (Box 13)
    - Miriam's Drum, 2005 (Box 13)
    - Mishka - "One Tree", 2005 (Box 13)
    - Miss Fairchild - "Ooh La La Sha Sha", 2007 (Box 13)
    - MisMatch - "Life Trip", 2007 (Box 13)
    - Miss Flag, 2006 (Box 13)
    - Miss Flag - "To Infinity", 2006 (Box 13)
    - Moshav Band - "Higher and Higher", 2005 (Box 13)
    - Moshav Band - "Misplaced" (3 copies), 2006 (Box 13)
    - Moshiach Oi! - "Better Get Ready", Undated (Box 13)
    - M.O.T. - "19.99", 1998 (Box 13)
    - Movement, The - "On Your Feet", 2004 (Box 13)
    - My-Lord Sound - "First Cut is the Deepest", Undated (Box 13)
    - My Second Surprist - "Avoidance as a Way of Life", 2005 (Box 13)
    - Nagler, JoAnneh - "I Burn", 2004 (Box 13)
    - Nessman, Less - "Bird's Eye View", 2004 (Box 13)
    - Next Shabbat Mixtape, 2009 (Box 13)
    - Next Shabbat Tunes, 2009 (Box 13)
    - Nigunim, Dafna, 2003 (Box 13)
    - Nissim, Itzchak - "Son of a Believer", Undated (Box 13)
    - No Flags, 1999 (Box 13)
    - No Man's Time - Recordings, 2008 (Box 13)
    - Noa - "Love Will Heal Us All", 2010 (Box 13)
    - Notebook Noise - "Snares, Hooks and Rhymebooks", 2008 (Box 13)
    - Nu Jewish Music - compilation, 2007 (Box 13)
    - Oman Hai Ensemble, Ha - "Writing from Within", 2004 (Box 13)
    - Onili - "First Kiss", Undated (Box 13)
    - Onili - "Games", 2007 (Box 13)
    - Our Hope Endures, 2002 (Box 13)
    - Over It - "Step Outside Yourself", 2006 (Box 13)
    - Oy Division, 2007 (Box 13)
    - Palm, 2003 (Box 13)
    - P Nuckle - "Colfax Satisfaction", 2003 (Box 13)
    - Pashm, Max - Never Mind the Balkans, 2008 (Box 14)
    - Paste Magazine Sampler (With Matisyahu Song), 2005 (Box 14)
    - Pharaoh's Daughter - "Daddy's Pocket", 1999 (Box 14)
    - PHP - "Hodu", 2008 (Box 14)
    - Picoso - "Vamoanos Pal Mole", 2007 (Box 14)
    - Pine, Shari, Undated (Box 14)
    - "Point Juncture, WA - "Mama Auto Boss", 2005 (Box 14)
    - Poppa's Kitchen - "A Rockin' Hanukkah", 2006 (Box 14)
    - Power Up the Planet - compilation (2 copies), 2009 (Box 14)
    - Radio Canada, Undated (Box 14)
    - Rafven - "Live", 2007 (Box 14)
    - Rafven - "Next Time We Take Your Instruments!", 2008 (Box 14)
    - Rahel, Tikkun - "Selected Meditations", 2004 (Box 14)
    - Rebbe Soul - "Change the World with a Sound", 2002 (Box 14)
    - Reb Jason - "Shabbat Rocks" (2 copies), 2004 (Box 14)
    - Recht, Rick - "Tov", 1999 (Box 14)
    - Road to Evenmind - "Diagnosis: Unsolved", 2010 (Box 14)
    - Roff, Joe - "A Better Place", 2003 (Box 14)
    - Rooftop Roots (2 copies), Undated (Box 14)
    - Rooftop Roots, vol. II (2 copies), Undated (Box 14)
    - Rooftop Roots, vol. III (2 copies), Undated (Box 14)
    - Rooftop Roots, vol. IV (2 copies), Undated (Box 14)
    - Ross, David - "The Power to Be", 2006 (Box 14)
    - Rothman, Chana - "We Can Rise", 2007 (Box 14)
    - Rubin, Rachel - "Ani L'dodi", 2004 (Box 14)
    - Sabbo & Kuti - "Better Days", 2010 (Box 14)
    - Safire Sky (2 copies), 2006 (Box 14)
    - Sage, Rachel - "Delancey St", Undated (Box 14)
    - Sagol 59 - "Make Room" (2 copies), 2008 (Box 14)
    - Sagol 59 - "Make Room" promo, 2008 (Box 14)
    - Sagol 59 - "Where Did We Go Wrong", 2002 (Box 14)
    - Sagol 59 - Unknown Hebrew title, 2006 (Box 14)
    - Sagol 59 - Unknown Hebrew title (2 copies), 2008 (Box 14)
    - Saints of Everyday Failures - "True Meaning of Survival", Undated (Box 14)
    - Shama, Gil Ron - "Soof" demo, 2010 (Box 14)
    - Shamir, Dave - "Late Bloomer" (2 copies), 2005 (Box 14)
    - Shantel - "Bucovina vol. 2 ep", 2005 (Box 14)
    - Shapiro, Andrew - "Numbers, Colors, and People" (2 copies), 2009 (Box 14)
    - Shapiro, Andrew - "Quiet Kissing" (2 copies), 2006 (Box 14)
    - Shemesh, Oneg - "Bring Us Together", Undated (Box 14)
    - Sheva - Israeli World Music, Undated (Box 14)
    - Shiraz - "Children of Israel, God is On Your Side", 2002 (Box 14)
    - Shirei HaLevi'im, 2009 (Box 14)
    - Shmuel, Rav - "Protocols" (2 copies), 2006 (Box 14)
    - Shondes, The, 2006 (Box 14)
    - Shoshan, Shimrit - "Keep it Movin'", 2010 (Box 14)
    - Showalter, Michael - "Sandwiches & Cats" (2 copies), 2007 (Box 14)
    - Showalter, Michael - "Sandwiches & Cats" demo (2 copies), Undated (Box 14)
    - Sh'siyah, Even - "Wake Up", 2005 (Box 14)
    - Shwachman, Matt - "Uncharted Territory", Undated (Box 14)
    - Silver, Julie - "It's Chanukah Time", 2006 (Box 14)
    - Sneakas - "Rap, Kicks & Politics" promo (2 copies), 2007 (Box 14)
    - Snyder, Shawn - "Romantic's Requiem", 2007 (Box 14)
    - Solomon, Sophie - "Poison Sweet Madeira", 2005 (Box 14)
    - Sound of Arabia, 2003 (Box 14)
    - Subatomic Sound System - "On All Frequencies", Undated (Box 14)
    - Survivors of the Holocaust - soundtrack, 1995 (Box 14)
    - So Called - "Ghettoblaster" (3 copies), 2007 (Box 14)
    - So Called - "Ghettoblaster" promo (3 copies), 2007 (Box 14)
    - So Called - "The So Called Seder" (2 copies), 2005 (Box 14)
    - So Called - "The So Called Seder" sound edit, 2005 (Box 14)
    - So Called - "The So Called Seder" promo (2 copies), 2005 (Box 14)
    - So Called - "You Are Never Alone" (3 copies), 2006 (Box 14)
    - So Called & David Krakauer - "Moskowitz and Loops of It", 2007 (Box 14)
    - Somerville Symphony Orkestar, 2011 (Box 14)
    - Soul Aviv, 2008 (Box 14)
    - Soulico - "Archeology: A Deep Dig into Israeli Grooves" (2 copies), Undated (Box 14)
    - Soulico - "Blend De Luxe: The Mixtape" (2 copies), 2008 (Box 14)
    - Soulico - "Delicatess" (3 copies), 2007 (Box 14)
    - Soulico - "Exotic on the Mixtape" (2 copies), 2009 (Box 14)
    - Soulico - "Exotic on the Speaker" (2 copies), 2009 (Box 14)
    - Soulico - "Exotic on the Speaker" promo (2 copies), 2009 (Box 14)
    - Soulico - "Milk and Honey" (2 copies), 2009 (Box 14)
    - Soulico - "Tel Avivin Mixtape" (2 copies), Undated (Box 14)
    - Steroe Sinai - "Biblegum Pop", 2008 (Box 14)
    - Superfly During Jazzfest, 2005 (Box 14)
    - Sway Machinery, The (3 copies), 2006 (Box 14)
    - Sway Machinery, The (2 copies), 2008 (Box 14)
    - Sway Machinery, The - "Hidden Melodies Revealed" (2 copies), 2009 (Box 14)
    - Sway Machinery, The - "Hidden Melodies Revealed" promo (2 copies), 2009 (Box 14)
    - Sway Machinery, The - "The House of Friendly Ghosts, vol. 1" (3 copies), 2010 (Box 14)
      One case does not contain a disk.
    - Sway Machinery, The - "The House of Friendly Ghosts, vol. 1" promo (2 copies), Undated (Box 14)
    - Sway Machinery, The - "Loot", 2000 (Box 14)
    - Tangerines, The (2 copies), 2006 (Box 14)
    - Ta-Shma - "Come Listen", 2006 (Box 14)
    - Tellerman, Judy - "Songs of the Code", 2007 (Box 14)
    - Temple - "Redeemable", 2005 (Box 14)
    - Teplow, Rebecca - "Kaveh / Hope", 2009 (Box 14)
    - Teva, Ha - "Skin of God", 2007 (Box 14)
    - Third Temple - "Sanctuary", 2008 (Box 14)
    - Third World Love - "Africa Mousse", 2005 (Box 14)
    - This is Chanukah, 2006 (Box 14)
    - Tobin, Amy - "4 Choices", 2003 (Box 14)
    - Tolcher, Michael - "I Am", 2004 (Box 14)
    - Turk, Matt - "Washington Arms", 2006 (Box 15)
    - Tzavellas, V'nessa - "Beautiful Things", 2006 (Box 15)
    - UBK - "Massive Soundtrack for the Modern Belly Dancer", Undated (Box 15)
    - Uncle Moishy - "Live", 2005 (Box 15)
    - Uncle Moishy and the Mitzvah Men's Judaica Store - "Mezzuzah", 2005 (Box 15)
    - United People of Zion, 2005 (Box 15)
    - V'achva, Ahava, 2005 (Box 15)
    - Vagabond Opera, 2006 (Box 15)
    - Vagabond Opera - "Get on the Train", 2003 (Box 15)
    - Valiant Woman - "Sista Warrior", c. 2003 (Box 15)
    - Vanya, 2008 (Box 15)
    - Version City Crew - "Sound Summit #1", 2003 (Box 15)
    - Vice - "CD/DVD #4" Presented by Tower Records, Undated (Box 15)
    - Vishiss, Undated (Box 15)
    - Wailing Wall - "Hospital Blossoms" (2 copies), Undated (Box 15)
    - Wailing Wall - "Low Hanging Fruit" (2 copies), c. 2009 (Box 15)
    - Wailing Wall - "Low Hanging Fruit" promo (2 copies), Undated (Box 15)
    - Wallick, Ben - "Dual Citizen", 2010 (Box 15)
    - Walters, Bobby BlackHat - "You Changed Your Mind Again", 2007 (Box 15)
    - Watcha Clan - "Radio Babel", 2011 (Box 15)
    - Watts, Elaine Hoffman - "Heart Beats", 2006 (Box 15)
    - Watts, Elaine Hoffman - "I Remember Klezmer", 2003 (Box 15)
    - Weinber, Adam - "On the Seventh Year" (2 copies), 2006 (Box 15)
    - Weinstein, Noam - "We're All Going There", 2006 (Box 15)
    - What I Like About Jew - "Unorthodox", Undated (Box 15)
    - White Shabbos - "Shabbos Holy Shabbos", 2004 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Tim - "Careful Love", 2009 (Box 15)
    - Winkler, Rabbi Gershon - "Shedding, Dying and Birthing:", Undated (Box 15)
    - Winkler, Rabbi Gershon - "Simple Unity", 2005 (Box 15)
    - Wiseman, Ron - "Mystical Mood", 2002 (Box 15)
    - Woofie Publishing Inc., 2009 (Box 15)
    - Woofie Publishing Inc. vol. IV - "Jameson Van Horn, Piano", 2009 (Box 15)
    - Ya Tafari - "The Psalmist", 2010 (Box 15)
    - Yankele - "Paris Klezmer", 2007 (Box 15)
    - Yardena y son Ladino, Undated (Box 15)
    - Yatan, Lev - "Wisdom of the Stream", 2002 (Box 15)
    - Ydov, Shlomo - "From Within the Silence" (2 copies), 2009 (Box 15)
    - Yiddish Soul, 2004 (Box 15)
    - Yitzhak & Sigalit Sadehu - "One", Undated (Box 15)
    - Yoel Ben Simhon & Sultana Ensemble, 2004 (Box 15)
    - Yom Hadash - "A New Day", 2008 (Box 15)
    - Yosef, Tomer - "Laughing Underground" (2 copies), 2008 (Box 15)
    - Yosef, Tomer - "Laughing Underground" promo (2 copies), 2008 (Box 15)
    - Young, Roland P. - "Twelve Elements", 2004 (Box 15)
    - Zebrina - "Trail of the Hunter Gatherers", 2010 (Box 15)
    - Zeda's Beat Box - "Kabbalat Shabbat", 2008 (Box 15)
    - Zetz! - "How Good it Is", 2010 (Box 15)
    - Zohar - "onethreeseven", 2001 (Box 15)
    - Zonk - "Our Five Worst Songs", 2004 (Box 15)
    - Zoyres Eastern European Wild Ferment - "Biserka!", 2008 (Box 15)
    - [Aksum] (2 copies)(in Hebrew), 2009 (Box 15)
    - [Alma Calma] (in Hebrew), 2008 (Box 15)
    - [Anneh Lee - Ehud B'nai] (in Hebrew), 2004 (Box 15)
    - [Halbum Harrison - Groovatron] (in Hebrew), 2010 (Box 15)
    - [Itay Lukatch] (in Hebrew), 2007 (Box 15)
    - [Kashy - Yotza Ha Hotzah] (in Hebrew), 2005 (Box 15)
    - [Soulico] (in Hebrew), 2006 (Box 15)
    - [Sukemah] (in Hebrew), 2011 (Box 15)
    - [Tomer Yosef - Tsohkus Matat Lazmeh] (in Hebrew), 2006 (Box 15)
    - 6 Points Fellowship, Undated (Box 15)
      Format: DVD
    - Alberstein, Chava - "Live in Berlin", Undated (Box 15)
    - Boom Pam, c. 2003 (Box 15)
    - Charlie Hunter Quintet - "Right Now Live", 2004 (Box 15)
    - Golem - "Live in Brooklyn", 2005 (Box 15)
    - "Golem, The", 1920 (Box 15)
    - Klingon Klez - "At the World Cafe Live", Undated (Box 15)
    - The LeeVees - "How Do You Spell: Channukkahh?", Undated (Box 15)
    - Matisyahu - "AOL Music Sessions", 2006 (Box 15)
    - Matisyahu - "En Concert", Undated (Box 15)
    - Matisyahu - "King Without a Crown", Undated (Box 15)
    - Matisyahu - "MTV 10 Spot" (2 copies), Undated (Box 15)
    - Matisyahu - "Recent National Television Appearances", Undated (Box 15)
    - Matisyahu - "A Short Documentary by David Baugnon", Undated (Box 15)
    - Matisyahu - "Youth" (2 copies), Undated (Box 15)
    - Meyer, Yael - "Common Ground" press kit, Undated (Box 15)
    - Merkava - "Live at Makor", 2007 (Box 15)
    - "Mifgash: Encountering Jewish Identity in the 21st Century", 2010 (Box 15)
    - Motion Theory - Music Video Reel, 2005 (Box 15)
    - Musicians on Call - Informational DVD, 2005 (Box 15)
    - Royal Vagabonds - "For the Kings Court", 2008 (Box 15)
    - Shama, Gil Ron - "Soof", Undated; 15 (Box 15)
    - "Sour: A Skate Documentary for Peace in the Middle East", 2007 (Box 15)
    - The Sway Machinery - "Live at Le Poisson Rouge", 2008 (Box 15)
    - "There is No Bad Boy", Undated (Box 15)
    - Uncle Moishy - "Jewish Holiday Songs", Undated (Box 15)
    - Uncle Moishy and the Mitzvah Men - vol. 6, Undated (Box 15)
    - Balkan Beat Box - "Nu Made (Remixes)" (2 copies), 2009 (Box 16)
      Format: Sound Disc: Analog, 33 1/3 rmp; 12 in.
    - Balkan Beat Box - "Nu Made (Remixes)" test, 2009 (Box 16)
    - Balkan Beat Box - "Nu Med" (2 copies), 2007 (Box 16)
    - Balkan Beat Box - "Nu Med" test (2 copies), 2009 (Box 16)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Self Titled (2 copies), 2005 (Box 16)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Self Titled test (3 copies), 2009 (Box 16)
    - Balkan Beat Box - Single (2 copies), 2005 (Box 16)
    - Matisyahu - "King Without a Crown" (2 copies), 2005 (Box 16)
      Format: Sound Disc: Analog, 45 rmp; 7 in.
    - Matisyahu - "King Without a Crown" Remix by Mike D (2 copies), 2005 (Box 16)
    - So Called - "You Are Never Alone", 2006 (Box 16)
    - Soulico - "Exotic on the Speaker" (2 copies), 2009 (Box 16)
    - Soulico - "Exotic on the Speaker" test (3 copies), Undated (Box 16)
    - Sway Machinery - 45 test (2 copies), Undated (Box 16)
    - Sway Machinery Featuring Khaira Arby (2 copies), Undated (Box 16)
    - Sway Machinery - "Hidden Melodies Revealed" (2 copies), 2009 (Box 16)
    - Wailing Wall, Undated (Box 16)
  - Subseries B: Papers removed from media
    - Abrahami, Fiona Nehama, Undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - After the Service, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Alan Cohen Experience, Undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Alma Calma, Undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Bible Raps - Teaching Resource Guide, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Bloom, Mark, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Chaki, Adam, Undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Fields, Irving, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Food Will Win the War (Rob), Undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Fox-Rosen, Avi - "Welcome to the Show", Undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Friedman, Hillel, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Gostein, Abby, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Hadash, Yom, Undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Hadara, Undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Heffner, Daniel, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - The HoodSka Explosive, Undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Jaffa Road, Undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Marie, Teena, Undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Mens Rea, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Miss Flag, Undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Noa, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Picoso, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Road to Evenmind, Undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Safire Sky, Undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Shamir, Dave, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Somerville Symphony Orkestar, Undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - System Restore, Undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Teplow, Rebecca, Undated (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Vanya, Undated (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Yankele - press kit, Undated (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Zetz!, Undated (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Loose papers - "Can Can" and "David Gould", Undated (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Series VI: Original Media